<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zoopedia</string>
    <string name="zoopedia">Zoopedia</string>
    <string name="teaching_by_playing_is_fun">Teaching by playing is fun</string>
    <string name="main_image">main_image</string>
    <string name="board_main_img">board_main_img</string>
    <string name="animal_1">animal_1</string>

    <!-- Animal 1 -->
    <string name="animal_Ard_title">Aardvark</string>
    <string name="animal_Ard_type">Orycteropus afer</string>
    <string name="animal_Ard_des">The aardvark (or Orycteropus afer) is a medium-sized insectivore that lives
    throughout Sub-Saharan Africa. They have pink-grey skin with sparse, coarse hair, large
    slender ears and an elongated head that ends in a pig-like snout. Males are slightly larger than females,
    but both sexes are generally between 105 and 130cm long, have a tail between 60 and 70cm,and
    weigh between 40 and 65kg.</string>

    <!-- African Buffalo -->
    <string name="animal_Buf_title">African Buffalo</string>
    <string name="animal_Buf_type">Syncerus caffer</string>
    <string name="animal_Buf_des">Living throughout Sub-Saharan Africa, the African buffalo
    (or Syncerus caffer) is the largest member of the cow
    family-bovids-found in the African wild. They are typically between
    1.7 and 3.4m in length, measure 1.0 to 1.7m tall, and are identifiable
    by their distinctive horns, which are broad, curved and unite in a \'boss\'
    in the centre of their forehead. The dominant male in a herd will often have the largest horns.</string>

    <!-- African Elephant -->
    <string name="animal_Ele_title">African Elephant</string>
    <string name="animal_Ele_type">Loxodonta</string>
    <string name="animal_Ele_des">The African elephant is native to Sub-Saharan Africa and lives in
        savanna,forests and mountains. African elephants are large and thickset with thick grey
        skin and a characteristic trunk that they use for vocalising, drinking and
        grasping food. Both male and female African elephants have tusks. Elephants
        are known for their intelligence and strong social bonds. Female herds bond
        for life and will remember and communicate with family members even if herds
        split up. Bonds are especially strong between mothers and their babies.</string>

    <!-- Bengal Tiger -->
    <string name="animal_Tig_title">Bengal Tiger</string>
    <string name="animal_Tig_type">Panthera Tigris</string>
    <string name="animal_Tig_des">The Bengal tiger (or Panthera Tigris)is native to India, Bangladesh,
    Nepal, Bhutan and Western China. It can live in all kinds of environments,
    including grassland, forests and mangroves, and will hunt large prey such as
    cloven-hoofed animals like goats, deer and cows(collectively known as ungulates).
    The Bengal tiger can be identified by its bright orange coat and brown or black stripes,
    along with a large head, muscular limbs and large teeth.</string>

    <!-- Bornean Orangutan -->
    <string name="animal_Mon_title">Bornean Orangutan</string>
    <string name="animal_Mon_type">Pongo pygmaeus</string>
    <string name="animal_Mon_des">the orangutan (or Pongo pygmaeus)is native to the island of Borneo, their range
    also spanning areas of Bornean Indonesia and Malaysia. They are large apes identifiable
    by their red fur and brown skin, while mature males also have distinct, large cheek pads
    and throat pouches used for making loud vocalizations to attract females. They are incredibly
    intelligent animals and gave been observed creating and using tools in the wild to acquire food.
    However, they cannot swim and their range is often limited by rivers that they cannot cross in
    the wild.</string>

    <!-- Jaguar -->
    <string name="animal_Jag_title">Jaguar</string>
    <string name="animal_Jag_type">Panthera onca</string>
    <string name="animal_Jag_des">The jaguar (or Panthera onca) is a species of big cat that lives
    throughout South America, Central America and Mexico, with rare individual sightings in the
    southern USA. Although they can live in multiple environment types, they prefer to be in
    dense forests, near swamps and rivers. They are stockily built compared to the other big
    cat species, weighing an average of between 56 and 96kg, and measuring 112 to 185cm long.
    They have yellow to orange fur with black rosette patterning, and a white underside.</string>


    <!-- Polar Bear -->
    <string name="animal_Bear_title">Polar Bear</string>
    <string name="animal_Bear_type">Ursus maritimus</string>
    <string name="animal_Bear_des">The polar bear (or Ursus maritimus) is a large ursine species
    that live in the Arctic Circle and the sub-Arctic regions. With a completely white coat,
    dark eyes and a dark nose, they are stocky in build, with sturdy legs and large feet that
    are well adapted to swimming. To minimise heat loss, the bears have small ears and a short
    tail. Males are between 2.4 and 3.0m long, weighing between 350 and 750 kg; females are
    between 1.8 and 2.4m long, weighing 150 to 250 kg. Both sexes feed on both ringed and
    bearded seals.</string>

    <!-- Giant Panda -->
    <string name="animal_Pan_title">Giant Panda</string>
    <string name="animal_Pan_type">Ailuropoda melanoleuca</string>
    <string name="animal_Pan_des">The giant panda (or Ailuropoda melanoleuca) is a species of bear
    native to the mountains of Central China. They have black and white fur in a distinctive
    pattern, with black legs, ears and circles around their eyes. Pandas feed almost
    exclusively on bamboo and, as a result, are extremely dependent on rich bamboo forests to
    survive. This is a low energy food, so pandas must eat a lot of it to live and spend most
    of their waking hours foraging and eating. Their low energy intake also means they produce
    very tiny and vulnerable cubs.</string>

    <!-- Giant Tiger Land Snail -->
    <string name="animal_Snail_title">Giant Tiger Land Snail</string>
    <string name="animal_Snail_type">Achatina achatin</string>
    <string name="animal_Snail_des">The giant tiger land snail (or Achatina achatina) is a large
    species of gastropod that lives in the woodland areas of West Africa; specifically Sierra
    Leone, Liberia, Ivory Coast, Ghana and Nigeria, among others. They have a grey body and a
    conical shell that\'s yellow, orange or tan with black stripes - the distinctive pattern
    being the inspiration for their name. The species is hermaphroditic, possessing both male
    and female reproductive parts, so there are no distinct \'males\' and \'females\'. However,
    small or sub-adult individuals have often not yet developed the reproductive parts and so
    may be considered \'males\'.</string>

    <!-- Gharial -->
    <string name="animal_Cro_title">Gharial</string>
    <string name="animal_Cro_type">Gavialis gangeticus</string>
    <string name="animal_Cro_des">Gharials (or Gavialis gangeticus) are a critically endangered
        species of crocodile native to the rivers of the Indian subcontinent. With recent
        estimations stating there are just 200 left in the wild, the dwindling population is now
        restricted to just four stretches of river in Nepal and North India. Their collapse in
        numbers has been caused by the increase in river pollution reducing the amount of fish
        in the water, as well as by sand-mining destroying sandbanks that are essential for
        egg-laying.</string>

</resources>